leadoutcome.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Statement

Protecting and respecting the privacy of our customers and those who use our website and our products and services is something you can count on from LeadOutcome. It is important that you understand how your personal information is collected and used. Personal information is any information that identifies you or would enable someone to contact you, such as your name, email address, phone number and other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. This privacy statement applies to all of LeadOutcome products and services any other sites owned or operated by LeadOutcome.

##  Information Collection and Use by Us

We are the sole owner of information collected on the Sites, except for contact lists and content that you provide to us in connection with your use of our products and services. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this privacy statement. We may obtain information that is provided during any voluntary or mandatory registration process, online payment transaction, request for technical support, when you call or email us, or when you visit our Sites. We collect information only as necessary to fulfill the purposes set forth in this privacy statement.

##  Choice/Opt-out

Our Anti-Spam Policy tolerates only permission-based email, see our AntiSpam Policy. You may choose to opt-out when sign-up for our email lists. You always have the opportunity to opt-out by following a link in the footer of all messages sent by us or by emailing us at [support@leadoutcome.com](mailto:support@leadoutcome.com). In addition, anyone receiving emails from us on behalf of our customers always has the opportunity to opt-out of email messages by using the opt-out link included in the link in the footer of the message. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited commercial email from us on behalf of any of our customers, you may report it to us at [abuse@leadoutcome.net](mailto:abuse@leadoutcome.net).

##  Cookies and Web Beacons

We use a variety of technologies on our Sites. Among these are cookies: a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer so that the website can remember your browser in the future. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a unique number. When you visit our Sites, open our email, encounter our services online (including on one of our customer's websites), or click on one of our banner ads or videos, we or an authorized third party may send you a cookie.

Cookies may be used by us in many ways: they allow us to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our Sites, track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs, and track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign, and to provide you with more relevant content. Cookies also allow us to track overall site usage and determine areas users prefer, as well as enable us to make your visit to our website easier by recognizing you when you return and help to provide you with a customized experience.

Information gathered through usage of a cookie is not linked to any personal identifying information, unless you become a trial or paying customer of ours. Once you submit personally identifiable information on our Sites (for example, by signing up to be a trial or paying customer of ours or by signing up for a seminar or white paper), we may link such information with cookies or other identifiers that are associated with your visit(s) to our Sites. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. If you choose to disable cookies, you may still use our Sites; however, you may have limited access to some areas within our Sites or a different experience. For more information on how to manage cookies in your web browser, see [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). We also provide you with an option to opt-out of receiving certain cookies associated with our online advertising (see the "Online Advertising" section below).

Some of our web pages, emails, and other online content may contain electronic images provided by us or authorized third parties known as web beacons, also known as single-pixel GIFs, which are invisible graphical images. These web beacons allow us to count users who have visited our Sites, seen our ads, or opened our email, and to track whether messages are shared using our social share features and, once shared, whether these messages are opened by the recipient. In addition, when you click on a link in an email, we record this individual response to allow us to customize our offerings to you. Web beacons collect only limited information, such as a cookie identifier, time and date of a page being viewed, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. Web beacons cannot be declined when delivered using a regular web page, but they can be refused when delivered by email. If you do not wish to receive web beacons by email, you will need to disable HTML images or refuse HTML (select Text only) emails via your email software.

##    
Import Wizard

The LeadOutcome import wizard uses a technology called Context.IO. When you use this feature you understand and agree that DokDok, Inc., its parent company, Return Path, Inc. and their affiliates (collectively "Context.IO Providers"), who provide Context.IO, will have access to your information and will be permitted to use that information in accordance with Return Path’s Privacy Policy. If you wish to opt-out of sharing your information with Context.IO Providers, you may do so at <https://optout.context.io/> or simple don't use the feature that allows you to automatically import emails by adding your email account.

You can learn more about how we use anonymous data in our Privacy FAQ (<https://context.io/privacy-faq>). Basically, we redact all personally identifiable information and then use the anonymous and aggregated reports to improve spam filters, report phishing attacks, improve deliverability, etc.
